stepstone.com 2018-05-09

# StepStone

### Purpose of Data Collection

One of the fundamentals of the relationship with StepStone – in fact of any relationship – is trust. With StepStone, you can trust that we are 100% committed to protecting your privacy. Our goal is to offer you, the user, a secure and risk free service. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains confidential, and is used only for the purposes described on our site.

#### What information do we collect?

On our web site we ask you to provide information which will enable us to enhance your visit to our web site.

#### Cookies

This site does not use persistent cookies.

#### Log Files and Statistics

In our Logfiles, we collect and store Internet Protocol addresses (IP addresses) for a limited period, as far as is necessary for data safety reasons. We also use IP addresses to create anonymous statistics, in order to measure the number of visitors to our web site (traffic) and for accounting purposes to calculate the number of clicks received via web sites of our business partners. We do not draw up user profiles or link IP addresses to personally identifiable information.

#### Illegal Content

Please note that you are solely responsible for all texts entered into our system or sent to us. Please ensure that you do not send us any attachments that contain viruses or worms.

The information you send us must be accurate and must not breach copyrights, trademarks or other intellectual property rights, contravene law, competition law or other applicable provisions, official regulations, the rights of third parties in general or public policy (“Illegal Content”). Please note that you undertake to indemnify us against all claims made against us as a consequence of your failure to prevent Illegal Content appearing in any information you provide.

#### Data Security

We use a variety of methods, such as firewalls, intrusion detection software and manual security procedures, to help protect the accuracy and security of your personal information and to prevent unauthorized access or improper use by third parties.

Please note that some employment contracts may not permit private use of the Internet during working hours or from your work place. Some employers systematically monitor unauthorised Internet activities on your work place. Although you are connected via a multiple network environment, you should be aware that there is a risk of unwanted access.

Please note that JavaScript technology is used on our web sites.

#### Interruption of services, withdrawal or changes of services, deletion of data

StepStone GmbH does not guarantee or warrant that the services are available at specific times. Disturbances, interruptions or a possible breakdown of the online service cannot be excluded by StepStone GmbH. Systematic backups of the servers are carried out regularly. In so far as data have been transferred to StepStone GmbH – regardless their form – we recommend that you create your own backup copies. StepStone GmbH reserves the right to delete a publication, without reason at any time without notice. The user has no right to claim publication. StepStone GmbH reserves the right to change, extend, limit or withdraw its services at any time. Therefore, StepStone GmbH shall not be liable for any deleted data or loss of data.

#### Links

Our web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our visitors to be aware of this when they leave StepStone GmbH, and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected on our web site.

#### Privacy Statement changes

Any changes to our privacy commitment will always be available here on our homepage so that our visitors are always aware of what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to third parties. At the bottom of this page you will find links to former versions of our Privacy Statement.

If you want to store this Privacy Statement, please press ctrl–s, to print press ctrl-p.

* * *

### Miscellaneous

If you should have any concerns or queries in relation to our Privacy Statement please contact us:

StepStone GmbH  
Axel-Springer-Str. 65  
10969 Berlin  
Amtsgericht Charlottenburg, HRB 129324 B  
UStID: DE249166292

T +49 30 398 0620  
F +49 30 398 09111

**Managing Directors:** Ralf Baumann, Thorsten Otte

E-mail : [info@stepstone.com](mailto:info@stepstone.com?subject=privacy)

This Privacy Statement replaces all other privacy statements previously applicable to the use of our web site.
